import React from 'react'

let cheese = {
    title: "Cheese Geography",
    questions: [
        {
            question: "Limburger cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["Belgium", "Limburgh", "Germany", "Poland"],
            correct: "Belgium"
        },
        {
            question: "Lancashire cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["France", "Great Britain", "Ireland", "Italy"],
            correct: "Great Britain"
        },
        {
            question: "Colby cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["United States", "France", "Great Britain", "Spain"],
            correct: "United States"
        },
        {
            question: "Gorganzola cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["France", "Italy", "Sicily", "Portugal"],
            correct: "Italy"
        },
        {
            question: "Prince-Jean cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["Belgium", "Great Britain", "Finland", "Canada"],
            correct: "Belgium"
        },
        {
            question: "Caerphilly cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["Great Britain", "Ireland", "France", "Denmark"],
            correct: "Great Britain"
        },
        {
            question: "Brick cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["United States", "Great Britain", "France", "Canada"],
            correct: "United States"
        },
        {
            question: "Telemea cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["Germany", "Spain", "Romania", "Poland"],
            correct: "Romania"
        },
        {
            question: "Graddost cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["Sweden", "Finland", "Denmark", "Great Britain"],
            correct: "Sweden"
        },
        {
            question: "Feta cheese comes from this country",
            answers: ["Greece", "Crete", "Italy", "France"],
            correct: "Greece"
        }
    ]
}

export default cheese